{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5278","name":"Det Receiving Cafe Stores LLC/Biggby","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Det Receiving Cafe Stores LLC ","licenseNumber":"200071","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365","coords":"-83.05472,42.35350","geojson":{"id":"5278","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.054716847,42.353501399]},"properties":{"name":"Det Receiving Cafe Stores LLC/Biggby","owner":"Det Receiving Cafe Stores LLC ","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"200071","establishmentid":"5278","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365","most_recent_license_date":"5/12/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4982","name":"Detroit Receiving Hospital","address":"4201 St Antoine","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622830","name":"Detroit Receiving Hospital","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51623123","name":"MMS/DMC Detroit Receiving Hosp. #51717","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622467","name":"Hungry Howie's","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5277","name":"Detroit Receiving Sub Shops LLC/Subway","address":"4201 St Antoine St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4996","name":"Children's Hospital of Michigan","address":"3901 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3870","name":"Subway #11819","address":"3901 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5279","name":"Childrens Cafe Stores LLC/Biggby","address":"3901 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1700","name":"Friendship Baptist","address":"3900 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"900","name":"Spain Middle/Elementary School","address":"3700 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"48796","inspectionDate":"2019-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Counter(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"8-304.11","violationDescription":"Upon acceptance of the PERMIT issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, the PERMIT HOLDER in order to retain the PERMIT shall:\r\n(A) Post the PERMIT in a location in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT that is conspicuous to CONSUMERS; \r\n(B) Comply with the provisions of this Code including the conditions of a granted VARIANCE as specified under § 8-103.12, and APPROVED plans as specified under § 8-201.12;\r\n(C) If a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT is required under § 8-201.13 to operate under a HACCP PLAN, comply with the plan as specified under § 8-103.12;\r\n(D) Immediately contact the REGULATORY AUTHORITY to report an illness of a FOOD EMPLOYEE or CONDITIONAL EMPLOYEE as specified under ¶ 2-201.11(B); \r\n(E) Immediately discontinue operations and notify the REGULATORY AUTHORITY if an IMMINENT HEALTH HAZARD may exist as specified under § 8-404.11;\r\n(F) Allow representatives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY access to the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT as specified under § 8-402.11;\r\n(G) Except as specified under ¶ (H) of this section, replace existing facilities and EQUIPMENT specified in § 8-101.10 with facilities and EQUIPMENT that comply with this Code if:\r\n(1) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement because the facilities and EQUIPMENT constitute a public health HAZARD or nuisance or no longer comply with the criteria upon which the facilities and EQUIPMENT were accepted,\r\n(2) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement of the facilities and EQUIPMENT because of a change of ownership, or\r\n(3) The facilities and EQUIPMENT are replaced in the normal course of operation;\r\n(H) Upgrade or replace refrigeration EQUIPMENT as specified under Subparagraph 3-501.16(A)(2)(b), if the circumstances specified under Subparagraphs (G)(1) - (3) of this section do not occur first, and 5 years pass after the REGULATORY AUTHORITY adopts this Code;\r\n(I) Comply with directives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY in regard to the PERMIT HOLDER'S FOOD ESTABLISHMENT or in response to community emergencies; \r\n(J) Accept notices issued and served by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY according to LAW; and \r\n(K) Be subject to the administrative, civil, injunctive, and criminal remedies authorized in LAW for failure to comply with this Code or a directive of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Dipper well","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49195","inspectionDate":"2019-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"8-304.11","violationDescription":"Upon acceptance of the PERMIT issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, the PERMIT HOLDER in order to retain the PERMIT shall:\r\n(A) Post the PERMIT in a location in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT that is conspicuous to CONSUMERS; \r\n(B) Comply with the provisions of this Code including the conditions of a granted VARIANCE as specified under § 8-103.12, and APPROVED plans as specified under § 8-201.12;\r\n(C) If a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT is required under § 8-201.13 to operate under a HACCP PLAN, comply with the plan as specified under § 8-103.12;\r\n(D) Immediately contact the REGULATORY AUTHORITY to report an illness of a FOOD EMPLOYEE or CONDITIONAL EMPLOYEE as specified under ¶ 2-201.11(B); \r\n(E) Immediately discontinue operations and notify the REGULATORY AUTHORITY if an IMMINENT HEALTH HAZARD may exist as specified under § 8-404.11;\r\n(F) Allow representatives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY access to the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT as specified under § 8-402.11;\r\n(G) Except as specified under ¶ (H) of this section, replace existing facilities and EQUIPMENT specified in § 8-101.10 with facilities and EQUIPMENT that comply with this Code if:\r\n(1) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement because the facilities and EQUIPMENT constitute a public health HAZARD or nuisance or no longer comply with the criteria upon which the facilities and EQUIPMENT were accepted,\r\n(2) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement of the facilities and EQUIPMENT because of a change of ownership, or\r\n(3) The facilities and EQUIPMENT are replaced in the normal course of operation;\r\n(H) Upgrade or replace refrigeration EQUIPMENT as specified under Subparagraph 3-501.16(A)(2)(b), if the circumstances specified under Subparagraphs (G)(1) - (3) of this section do not occur first, and 5 years pass after the REGULATORY AUTHORITY adopts this Code;\r\n(I) Comply with directives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY in regard to the PERMIT HOLDER'S FOOD ESTABLISHMENT or in response to community emergencies; \r\n(J) Accept notices issued and served by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY according to LAW; and \r\n(K) Be subject to the administrative, civil, injunctive, and criminal remedies authorized in LAW for failure to comply with this Code or a directive of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Dipper well","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Counter(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42765","inspectionDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"CUSTOMER ORDER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide clear easy to read time marks."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of Thin tipped/digital thermometer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Dipper well","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-07-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"39465","inspectionDate":"2017-06-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 4 hours during continual use","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"In the Prep cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"IMPROPER Food Storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"violationCode":"2-102.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall demonstrate this knowledge by compliance with this Code, by being a certified FOOD protection manager who has shown proficiency of required information through passing a test that is part of an ACCREDITED PROGRAM, or by responding correctly to the inspector's questions as they relate to the specific FOOD operation. (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not demonstrate required knowledge","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Knowledge is to be obtained through an approved training program."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Dipper well","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5278"}}